

Artyom Butorin

iOS Developer

I'm an iOS developer with over I year of commercial development experience and more than 2 years of pet-project creation. I have a bachelor's degree in system programming engineering. I also completed iOS mobile development training and interned on a commercial project at Clevertec. I'm currently working at Corpus.by on a project to develop an application to work with various AI technologies.

Contact Info

- **+375 (25) 674-93-54**
- butorin.artiom@gmail.com
- ∅ @butorin_artyom
- in linkedin.com/in/butorinartyom
- github.com/ArtiDeln
- Gomel, Belarus (or remote)

Education

Francisk Skorina Gomel State University 2017 - 2022

Speciality:

Informatics and programming technologies

Qualification:

System programmer engineer

Courses

iOS mobile development training Clevertec - 2021

Languages

- English
- Belarusian Native
- Native Russian

All links



This QR code redirects to a page with my personal links

Work Experience

Corpus.by

iOS Developer

May 2023 - Present

Developing a new version of the app that works with advanced AI technology

- Migrating an app from UIKit to SwiftUI
- Implementation of in-app purchases and **PayWall**
- Development and implementation of app functionality
- Using Realm as a database
- · Getting localization using API and storing it in the database
- Implementation of custom views

Clevertec

Trainee iOS Developer

Nov 2021 - Feb 2022

Commercial mobile banking application development (NDA)

- Developed and integrated new features to expand the functionality of the application.
- Created UI in code
- Developed of custom UI components
- · Code-review and bug-fix

Skills

- Swift
- UIKit
- SnapKit
- SwiftUI
- UserDefaults
- StoreKit
- CocoaPods, SwiftPM
- Autolayout
- MVVM, MVVM+C, MVC
 URLSession

- Realm
- GCD
- Stinsen
- ARC

Tools

- Xcode
- Git

Jira

- Figma
- Notion

- Postico
- MongoDB
- Postman